<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Virtual machine on Dom&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/virtual-machine/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Virtual machine on Dom&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/virtual-machine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Debian Wheezy 64 Vagrant Base Box</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2012/02/debian-wheezy-64-vagrant-base-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2012/02/debian-wheezy-64-vagrant-base-box/</guid>
      <description>In the same spirit as Debian Squeeze 64 Vagrant Base Box this post describes a new Vagrant base box for Debian Wheezy. Wheezy is currently the unstable version of Debian, meaning the box is a constant work in progress. I will update this post each time the box is upgraded.
Quickstart To get up and running you just need to:
gem install vagrant vagrant box add wheezy64 http://dl.dropbox.com/u/937870/VMs/wheezy64.box vagrant init wheezy64 vagrant up Details The base box has the following characteristics:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debian Squeeze 64 Vagrant Base Box Upgrade Recipe</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2011/08/debian-squeeze-64-vagrant-base-box-upgrade-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2011/08/debian-squeeze-64-vagrant-base-box-upgrade-recipe/</guid>
      <description>After building a Vagrant base box, Vagrant and Virtual Box updates incurred lots of upgrades. This article gives a recipe to do that quickly and efficiently.
Build a new environment mkdir /tmp/upgrade cd /tmp/upgrade vagrant init squeeze64 vagrant up vagrant halt At that point the VM is stoped. Launch it from the Virtual Box GUI and mount the guest tools (Host+D).
Upgrade Log into the VM through vagrant:
vagrant ssh Upgrade the OS and the tools:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debian Squeeze 64 Vagrant Base Box</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2011/03/debian-squeeze-64-vagrant-base-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2011/03/debian-squeeze-64-vagrant-base-box/</guid>
      <description>Lately I needed to test a project under Debian Squeeze 64 bit. I found several 32 bit boxes but no 64 bits. So I decided to build one of my own.
Quickstart To get up and running you just need to:
gem install vagrant vagrant box add squeeze64 http://dl.dropbox.com/u/937870/VMs/squeeze64.box vagrant init squeeze64 vagrant up Details The base box has the following characteristics:
 275Mb in it&amp;rsquo;s packaged form; 8Gb hard drive; Debian Squeeze with a linux-image-2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>